# EBINYASI ONYINYECHI OLUEBUBE

NO 6 FREEDOM CLOSE NYSC RD GBAZANGO KUBWA, ABUJA

08033588034

onyxabc92@gmail.com

#### **CAREER OBJECTIVE**

I aim to proffer quality pharmaceutical care services and collaborate with others for the optimization of the client's quality of life. My previous work experiences have refined my managerial, communication and time management skills. I look to use these skills to achieve optimum results should you choose to make me a part of your team.

#### **SKILLS**

- Proficient in basic and advanced computer applications: Software/Applications (MS Word, MS PowerPoint, MS Excel, MS Access, eDispenser, etc).
- Proactive Attitude.
- Excellent Verbal and Written Communication Skills.
- · Excellent Interpersonal and Time Management Skills.
- Creativity and Multitasking.
- Analytical thinker, Dynamic and Solution driven.
- Good team player and a positive team motivator.
- Skilled at Inventory Management.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### SUPERINTENDENT PHARMACIST - LAZEK PHARMACY LTD

#### JANUARY 2019 – JANUARY 2021

- Prescription review, filling and dispensing.
- Procurement and general inventory management.
- Task delegation, monitoring and supervision of pharmacy attendants.
- Ensuring proper and smooth running of services in the Pharmacy.
- Conduct appropriate public awareness programs and Health campaigns.
- Regularly providing analytical support to the director & stakeholders.

# NYSC / PHARMACIST - NATIONAL INDUSTRIAL COURT OF NIGERIA STAFF CLINIC ABUJA FCT

#### **NOV 2017 - NOV 2018**

- Prescription review, filling and dispensing.
- Inventory management; Procurement, Distribution and Storage of pharmaceuticals.
- Supervising and directing technician's work flow
- Public Health Campaigns; HANDWASHING, a practice that curbs a plethora of infectious diseases.
- Actively involved in the creation of the Essential Drug List for the staff clinic.

#### SDG ADVOCATE – FCT SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT GOALS GROUP

#### **NOV 2017 - OCT 2018**

- I participated in several public health campaigns with the group, all focused on achieving Goal 3 of the SDGs; 'Good Health and Wellbeing'. Some of these outreaches /campaigns include:
- Deworming program & Vitamin A administration of over 200 children aged 6months to 16years in Jikoko community of Mpappe, Abuja.
- Free viral Hepatitis Screening and Counseling of members of Jikoko community, Mpappe Abuja.
- Hope for the Blind Project for the students of 'School of the Blind Jabi Abuja'.
- Breast Cancer Awareness Campaign to the Market women in Wuse market Abuja.
- Blood Drive Project; a free voluntary blood donation event in collaboration with the National Blood Transfusion Service (NBTS).

# LOCUM PHARMACIST - AIREN PHARMACY LTD, JABI ABUJA.

#### **JUNE 2017 - DECEMBER 2020**

- Prescription review, filling and dispensing.
- Task delegation, monitoring and supervision of nursing staff and pharmacy attendants.
- Ensuring proper and smooth running of services in the Pharmacy.
- Public awareness programs on the menace of drug abuse and misuse, antibiotic resistance, adverse drug reactions, etc.

#### INTERN PHARMACIST - FEDERAL MEDICAL CENTER KEFFI

#### **JUNE 2016 - MAY 2017**

- Prescription review, filling and dispensing.
- Provision of drug information and counselling to patients and caregivers.
- Provision of Drug information to Physicians and other Healthcare personnel for optimized patient care.
- Compounding, packaging and labelling of extemporaneous pharmaceuticals.
- Inventory management; Procurement, Distribution and Storage of pharmaceuticals.
- Participated in Public Health awareness campaigns; on the Ravages of Enteric Fever in Keffi, and on Steven Johnson Syndrome.

#### PHARMACIST - MEBLINK PHARMACY OWERRI, IMO STATE

#### **AUGUST 2015 - MAY 2016**

- Organized people and resources to manage projects and train staff members and stakeholders.
- Organized seminars, planned projects and prepared budgets.
- Monitored projects, analysed progress and prepared reports.

### **EDUCATION & QUALIFICATIONS**

- CLINICAL MANAGEMENT OF HIV PATIENTS University of Washington MAR 2019 -JUN 2019
- BACHELOR OF PHARMACY University of Port Harcourt, Choba Rivers State 2015
- WEST AFRICAN SENIOR SCHOOL CERTIFICATE (WASSCE) Federal Government Girls College Owerri, Imo State / 2008

## ORGANISATIONAL MEMBERSHIP

Electoral Coordinator

2014 - 2015

Pharmaceutical Association of Nigerian Students

Assistant Class Representative

2012 - 2015

Assistant Follow-up Secretary

2012 - 2014

Christ Ambassador Students Outreach

Course Representative

(Pharmaceutics) 2011-2012

# **RESEARCH AND PUBLICATION**

PHARMACEUTICAL QUALITY OF SEVEN CEFTRIAXONE SODIUM BRANDS MARKETED IN SOUTHERN NIGERIA

**British Journal of Pharmaceutical Research** 

November 21, 2015

# **AWARDS**

BEST INTERN PHARMACIST AWARD 2017
NIGERIAN ASSOCIATION OF HOSPITAL AND ADMINISTRATIVE
PHARMACISTS (NAHAP) FMC KEFFI

# **REFEREES**

Available on Request